Hadis Sulejmani

Software Developer

ul.1 br.212 Saraj Skopje, North Macedonia

Skills

I am experienced building maintainable, efficient, clean and testable code with Java and Javascript. I'm proficient in API design and data modeling and also have a good understanding of concurrent software challenges. I have intermediate SQL Database skills in a production environment. I am continuously learning and working with a range of technologies (for example, Go, Nodejs, Nextjs, Terraform, Kubernetes, C#, .NET). From the personal side, I am proactive and enthusiastic to customer best interests and ongoing process improvements. Have so much curiosity and passion for building software and am a great team player.

Experience

Freelancer / Software Developer

Jul 2019 - Present, 1 yr 10 mos

- Currently prototyping a web app for helping communities get easier involved on climate change initiatives.
- Developed an ERP System for a meat products manufacturer.
- Communicated with businesses to identify high-level and detailed requirements.
- Led projects from concept through completion. Liaised with project managers, business stakeholders, and other team members.
- Built a proof-of-concept open-source search engine specialized for development purposes to reduce the time developers waste searching on the web.
- Translated business specifications into the program design.
- Designed and developed an Angular 11 web application that consumes data from JSONPlaceholder API, designed as an Instagram clone.
- Designed and developed an Android mobile app for forecasting weather, a school project.
- Provided technical support and troubleshooting and installed hardware and software.
- Helped and mentored other developers from various backgrounds.

Technologies: Java, Spring Boot, Javascript, Nodejs, C#, .NET, Python, Django, Angular, React, AWS, ERPNext, HTML, CSS, RxJS, Bootstrap, PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, GIT

Freelancer / Graphic Designer

Jul 2019 - Present, 1 yr 10 mos

- Designed packaging designs for food brands that sell in Düsseldorf, Germany and also in North Macedonia.
- Designed logos for different industries including small and medium sized companies.

Technologies: Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Gimp, Inkscape

SAASPASS, Aradiom / Front-end Intern

Sep 2018 - Feb 2019, 6 mos

- Maintained and improved the client portal Angular 2.0 application.
- Initiated the migration of our client portal from Angular to React.
- Conducted R&D (research and development) for libraries and ways to improve our codebase.

Technologies: Angular, HTML, CSS, RxJS, Bootstrap, Material Design, Spring Boot

Education

Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering, FINKI / BS

Sep 2017 - Oct 2020, Skopje

Throughout my studies there have been four main areas of focus for me: Web Development, Algorithms and Design Patterns, System Security, Business Management.